ILR School Office of Special Projects and School Relations Miscellany /3097
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Office of Special Projects and School Relations Miscellany
1965-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3097
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Collection of accounts of special projects such as Faculty-Alumni Seminars, correspondence, Continuing Ed-Summer programs, Alumni Affairs, conferences, oral histories, etc.
3082437
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Office of Special Projects and School Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3082437
- ILR Alumni: Listing of Individuals in various areas to visit, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cornell University Messenger Service, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 10th Faculty-Alumni Seminar: NY City, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Faculty-Alumni Seminar Ithaca, New York, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Faculty-Alumni Seminar: New York City, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Faculty-Alumni Seminar: New York City, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Faculty-Alumni Seminar: New York City, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Faculty-Alumni Seminar: New York City, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Faculty-Alumni Seminar: New York City, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Faculty-Alumni Seminar: New York City, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Faculty-Alumni Seminar: New York City, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Faculty-Alumni Seminar: New York City, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Dean Moore Report on Alumni Activities, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Correspondence rel. ILR Alumni Assn. meeting in New York City, Nov. 5, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ST-30 - ILR Alumni, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Alumni (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Alumni, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Old Info, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Continuing Ed-Summer Program, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- ILR - Publications Announcements, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- ILR Alumni (Prominent), 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- ST-31 Faculty-Alumni Seminar, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Alumni Affairs Oct. 1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- NYSSILR - Alumni News V. 15-18, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Directory of Living Alumni, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- International Conference on Trends in Industrial and Labor Relations, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Directory of Living Alumni, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ILR Alumni Directory, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ILR Alumni Directory, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- International Conference on Trends in Industrial and Labor Relations, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Pierce '78, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Oral History, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Pierces Lecture, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Labor Day Convocation, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Pierce Lectures 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Steingut '77, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Steingut 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Steingut '79, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Steingut '80, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Pierce General, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Pierce '79, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Pierce Reel 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Reel Tape
- Pierce Reel 2 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Reel tape
- Pierce Reel 3 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Pierce Reel 4 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Pierce Reel 5 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Pierce Reel 6 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Pierce Reel 7 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Pierce Reel 8 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Pierce Reel 8 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Pierce Reel 9 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Pierce Reel 10 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Pierce Reel 11 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Pierce Reel 12 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Buffalo-Spring Productivity Conf. '75, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Eco. Conf. Important, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Eco. Conf., 1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- June, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Conclusions and Recommendations Buffalo L-M Conf., 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- A, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Participants, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Replies to Commissioner/ Legislators Invite Eco. Conf. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Jobs and Economic Development in New York State, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- The Labor Management Conference, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- List of Names that Have Been Sent to Statler Hilton for Housing, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- State Eco. Conference Registrations - Labor, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- State Eco. Conference Registrations - Management, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- State Eco. Conference Registrations - Management, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- State Eco. Conference Registrations - Labor, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Slide Sound A/V, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- FS10-1 Pierce Lectures - David A. Morse, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Development, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Gorwin, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Programs + Chairman + Survey, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- State of the State's Eco. Conf., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Labor-Management Conf., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Labor-Management Conf., 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Pierce Lecture - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Pierce - General, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Pierce Memorial Lectur., 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Pierce Coleman, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Frank W. Pierce, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Pierce Lectures State. Of Transaction, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Pierce-- 1967 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Pierce-- Kaldor, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Pierce-- Kaldor Dinner, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Pierce Lectures, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Pierce-- Committee and Dean, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Pierce Lectures Goldberg, Wirtz and Shultz, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Pierce Lectures Goldberg, Wirtz and Shultz, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)